Guide to the Yale University Press Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Administrative records, including directors and board of governors files, circa 1938-2004; Accession 2006-A-052
  - YUP Board of Governors (General)/Misc. Planning
    - FRIENDS
      - FRIENDS SPECIAL EVENTS (Box 14)
        - Visit of Lord Wilson to the Press, 1998 January 21 (Box 14, Folder 529)
  - YUP Associations/Organizations
    - Academy of American Poets (Box 15, Folder 530)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (Box 15, Folder 531)
    - American Book Awards, The (TABA) (Box 15, Folder 532)
    - American Musicology Society, Inc. (Box 15, Folder 533)
    - American Philosophical Society (Box 15, Folder 534)
    - Bibliography of American Literature (Box 15, Folder 535)
    - Connecticut Academy of Arts and Sciences, The (Box 15, Folder 536)
    - Connecticut Public Television (Box 15, Folder 537)
    - Holocaust Library, The (Box 16, Folder 539)
    - Horton International (Box 16, Folder 540)
    - International Association of Scholarly Publishers (Box 16, Folder 541)
    - International Center of New Haven, The (Box 16, Folder 542)
    - Thomas Jefferson Center for the Protection of Free Expression, The (Box 16, Folder 543)
    - Library of America, The (Box 16, Folder 544)
    - Morgan [Pierpont] Library, The (Box 16, Folder 545)
    - National Enquiry, Governing Board of (Box 16, Folder 546)
    - New Haven Downtown Council (Box 16, Folder 547)
    - New Haven Free Public Library (Box 16, Folder 548)
    - New Haven - Ninth Square (Box 16, Folder 549)
    - New York Historical Society, The (Box 16, Folder 550)
    - New York Historical Society - Audubon's "Birds of America" (Box 16, Folder 551)
    - New York Public Library (Box 16, Folder 552)
    - New York Public Library - Book Preservation (Box 16, Folder 553)
    - New York Times (Box 16, Folder 554)
    - Scholarly Publishing - A Journal for Authors and Publishers (Box 16, Folder 555)
    - Society for Scholarly Publishing (Box 16, Folder 556)
    - Society for Scholarly Publishing - International Publishing Panel: Chicago, 1992 June 19 (Box 16, Folder 557)
    - Society of American Historians, Inc., The (Box 16, Folder 558)
    - United States Publishers Association, Inc. (Box 16, Folder 559)
    - University Publishing Association (Box 16, Folder 560)
  - YUP Distributors/Publishers/University Presses
    - Distributors
      - Art Distribution (Box 16, Folder 561)
      - Aperture (Box 16, Folder 562)
      - Book Centre (Box 16, Folder 563)
      - Book and Film Services (Box 16, Folder 564)
      - Bowker Company, R.R. (Box 16, Folder 565)
      - Japan Sales Office (Box 16, Folder 566)
      - MUSE (Karl Katz) (Box 16, Folder 567)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 568)
      - Unilibros (Box 16, Folder 569)
    - Publishers
      - Barber, A. Richard and Assoc. (Box 16, Folder 570)
      - Batsford Limited, B.T. (Box 16, Folder 571)
      - Benjamin, Roy (Box 16, Folder 572)
      - Brenzel Publishing, Inc. (Box 16, Folder 573)
      - Chelsea House Publishers (Box 16, Folder 574)
      - Eriksson, Paul S. Publisher (Box 16, Folder 575)
      - Godine, David R., Publisher, Inc. (Box 16, Folder 576)
      - HarperCollins Publishers, Inc. (Box 16, Folder 577)
      - Hudson Hills Press (Box 16, Folder 578)
      - Alfred A. Knopf (Box 16, Folder 579)
      - Norton, Jeffrey, Publishers, Inc. (Box 16, Folder 581)
      - Penguin Book Limited (Box 16, Folder 582)
      - Publishers Weekly (Box 16, Folder 583)
      - Random House, Inc. (Box 16, Folder 584)
      - Simon and Schuster (Box 16, Folder 585)
      - W.W. Norton and Co., Inc. (Box 16, Folder 586)
    - University Presses
      - University of California Press - Consulting (Box 16, Folder 587)
      - Cambridge University Press (Box 16, Folder 588)
      - Catholic University of America Press (Box 16, Folder 589)
      - University of Chicago Press (Box 16, Folder 590)
      - Columbia University Press (Box 16, Folder 591)
      - Columbia University Press - Consulting (Box 16, Folder 592)
      - Cornell University Press (Box 17, Folder 593)
      - Dartmouth School of Business (Box 17, Folder 594)
      - Edinburgh University Press (Box 17, Folder 595)
      - Harvard University Press (Box 17, Folder 596)
      - Indiana University Press (Box 17, Folder 597)
      - Johns Hopkins University Press (Box 17, Folder 598)
      - Michigan University Press (Box 17, Folder 599)
      - MIT University Press (Box 17, Folder 600)
      - University Press of New England (Box 17, Folder 601)
      - North Carolina University Press (Box 17, Folder 602)
      - Ohio University Press (Box 17, Folder 603)
      - Oklahoma University Press (Box 17, Folder 604)
      - Oxford University Press (Box 17, Folder 605)
      - Princeton University Press Visiting Committee (Box 17, Folder 606)
      - Rutgers University Press (Box 17, Folder 607)
      - Stanford University Press (Box 17, Folder 608)
      - University of Texas Press (Box 17, Folder 609)
      - University of Toronto Press (Box 17, Folder 610)
      - University of Washington Press (Box 17, Folder 611)
      - Wesleyan University Press (Box 17, Folder 612)
      - Wesleyan University Press - Search Committee Round I (Box 17, Folder 613)
      - Wesleyan University Press - Search Committee Round II (Box 17, Folder 614)
      - University Press Articles (Box 17, Folder 615)
      - University Presses, Misc. (Box 17, Folder 616)
      - Correspondence, Palladium Press (Box 17, Folder 617)
      - Temple University Press (Box 17, Folder 618)
      - Duke University Press (Box 17, Folder 619)
      - Columbia University Press graphs, etc. (Box 17, Folder 620)
  - YUP CCC (Culture and Civilization of China)
    - Articles of Incorporation (Box 17, Folder 621)
    - Correspondence, 1993-2002 (Box 17, Folder 622 - 631)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 18, Folder 632 - 634)
    - Peck, James (Box 18, Folder 635)
    - Meeting with J. Peck, 1998 October 14 (Box 18, Folder 636)
    - Peck Visit to Beijing, 2000- 2001 (Box 18, Folder 637)
    - Beijing 2003 (Box 18, Folder 638)
    - China Trip 1994 (Box 18, Folder 639)
    - Team Meetings
      - AAP Hawkins Prize (Three Thousand Years of Chinese Painting) (Box 18, Folder 640)
    - Advisory Board (Box 18)
      - Chant (Box 18, Folder 641)
      - Talk at Hobe Sound, 2002 December 5 (Box 18, Folder 642)
      - American Council of Learned Societies (Box 18, Folder 643)
      - Bush, George (Box 18, Folder 644)
      - Block, Paul R. (Box 18, Folder 645)
      - Cahill, Jim (Box 18, Folder 646)
      - Chan, Ronnie C. (Box 18, Folder 647)
      - Ellsworth, Robert (Box 18, Folder 648)
      - Gray, Christopher (Box 18, Folder 649)
      - Hamm, Edward (Correspondence) (Box 18, Folder 650)
      - Mellon, Mrs. Timothy (Box 18, Folder 651)
      - Phathanothai, Sirin (Correspondence) (Box 18, Folder 652)
      - Phathanothai, Sirin (Contract) (Box 18, Folder 653)
      - Shen, T.P. (Box 18, Folder 654)
      - Spencer, Ronald (Box 18, Folder 655)
      - Thailand, Prince of (Princess Sirinthorne) (Box 18, Folder 656)
      - Thailand, Queen of (Yale and the Queens of Thailand) (Box 18, Folder 657)
      - Update Reports (Box 18, Folder 658)
      - U.S. China Business Council Board of Directors (Box 18, Folder 659)
      - U.S. China Business Council Gala, 2000 June 12 (Box 18, Folder 660)
      - Visa Letters (Box 18, Folder 661)
      - Watt, James C.Y. (Box 18, Folder 662)
      - Weber, Charlotte (correspondence) (Box 18, Folder 663)
      - Wu, Ivy (Box 18, Folder 664)
      - Wusun, Lin (Box 18, Folder 665)
      - Youyi, Huang (Box 18, Folder 666)
      - Zhenguan, Yang (China International Publishing Group) (Box 18, Folder 667)
      - Agreements (Box 18, Folder 668)
      - General Statement of Understanding (Box 19, Folder 669)
      - Memorandums, signed (Box 19, Folder 670)
      - Prospectus/Synopsis (Box 19, Folder 671)
    - Series
      - Basic Texts of Classical Chinese Writing (Box 19, Folder 679)
      - Archeology (Box 19, Folder 680)
      - Architecture (Box 19, Folder 681)
      - Calligraphy (Box 19, Folder 682)
      - Ceramics (Box 19, Folder 683)
      - Classical Chinese Writing (Handbook) (Box 19, Folder 684)
      - Classical Chinese Writing, Companion to (Box 19, Folder 685)
      - English Dictionary (Box 19, Folder 686)
      - Medicine and Pharmacology (Box 19, Folder 687)
      - Philosophy (Box 19, Folder 688)
      - Sculpture (Box 19, Folder 689)
      - Three Thousand Years of Chinese Painting (Box 19, Folder 690)
      - Treasures of China Buddhist Art (Box 19, Folder 691)
      - Visual Arts Book (Box 19, Folder 692)
      - China International Publishing Group (CPIG) (Box 19, Folder 693)
      - Conference - CC/ACLS, 1992 February 21 (Box 19, Folder 694)
      - Beijing, 1992 March-April (Box 19, Folder 695)
      - Photographs (Box 19, Folder 696)
      - Publicity (Box 19, Folder 697)
      - Publicity Questions and Answers (Box 19, Folder 698)
      - Press release, 1991 September 11 (Box 19, Folder 699)
      - Publications Committee - Report to, 1994 November 21 (Box 19, Folder 700)
      - Yang's Visit, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 701)
    - Trips to China:
      - Levin China Trip, 2001 May (Box 19, Folder 702)
      - 1995 Oct 18-Nov 4 (Box 19, Folder 703)
      - 1992 Mar (Box 19, Folder 704)
      - Travel info for Future Trips to China (Box 19, Folder 705)
      - Trip to Texas, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 706)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH):
      - China Project: Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 707)
      - China Project: RO-22572-92 (Collaborative Projects) (Box 20, Folder 708)
      - Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 709)
      - 5 Year Plan (Box 20, Folder 710)
      - Documents of Communism (Box 20, Folder 711)
      - Brochure, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 712)
      - Brochure (Box 20, Folder 713)
      - CCC Invoices, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 714)
      - Budget (Box 20, Folder 715)
      - Lease (Office Space in NY) (Box 20, Folder 716)
      - Publication Committee Packets, 2003- (Box 20)
      - China Project: Hong Kong Speeches (Box 20, Folder 717)
      - Supp. 6 RP's (Box 20, Folder 718)
      - Update Reports/Call Reports (Box 20, Folder 719)
  - YUP Funds, Assignment of Funds, etc.
    - YUP Possible Endowment Drive, 1974- (Box 22, Folder 721)
    - Reports to Mr. Stoddard (Box 22, Folder 722)
    - Yale History Publication Funds, 1970- (Box 22, Folder 739)
    - Gift Letters, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 740)
    - Public Libraries in India - Mr. Crowell (Box 22, Folder 741)
    - Providence…(illegible) (Box 23, Folder 750)
    - Mathies (Box 23, Folder 755)
    - Tew (Box 23, Folder 757)
    - YUP Special Fund (Box 23, Folder 759)
    - Yale University Treasurer's Office re: Funds (Box 23, Folder 760)
    - Lewis - WALPOLE (Box 23, Folder 762)
    - Yale Law School (Box 23, Folder 764)
    - George B. Taylor - Political Union (Box 23, Folder 765)
    - GPD-NVD (Box 23, Folder 766)
    - Publication Funds: List of Funds and Descriptions of each (Deeds of Gifts) (Box 23, Folder 767)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Grants (Box 23, Folder 787)
    - Brachman, Malcolm (gift to YUP for Yale Judaica Series) (Box 23, Folder 790)
    - Henry J. Fisher Gift (Box 23, Folder 806)
    - E.S. Furniss - Subsidies (Box 23, Folder 809)
    - A. Whitney Griswold Fund (Box 23, Folder 810)
    - Gifts to YUP (Hilles) (Box 23, Folder 813)
    - Julius Kahn Gift Account (Box 23, Folder 816)
    - Peter Maffitt Gift (Box 23, Folder 820)
    - Carl L. Selden Gift (Box 23, Folder 827)
    - John Hay Whitney (Box 23, Folder 837)
    - Yale University Funds (as a result of Univ. Directives) - $10,000 annually (Box 24, Folder 839)
    - Yale University Library (Box 24, Folder 840)
    - Description of Press Funds Held by the University, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 842)
    - Publication Funds - Recipients of Volumes (Box 24, Folder 845)
    - Yale Review, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 847)
    - YU $22,000 Grant (for publication of the younger faculty) (Young Scholars Fund) (Box 24, Folder 848)
    - Report to the Treasurer, 1938-1939 (Box 24)
    - Report to the Treasurer, 1963-1964 (Box 24)
  - YUP Contracts - Pending: BOOKS
    - Albert, Herman W.A. Mozart (Box 5, Folder 851)
    - American Icons (Box 21, Folder 852)
    - Blum, John - On Governing America (Box 21, Folder 854)
    - Borchardt, Georges (Box 5, Folder 855)
    - Bundy/Goldstein - Untitled Book on Vietnam (Box 21, Folder 856)
    - Broadhead, Richard (Box 21, Folder 857)
    - Burrow, Gerard - Passing the Torch (Box 5, Folder 858)
    - Chen, Lung-Chi - An Intro. To Contemporary International Law (Revised) (Box 5, Folder 859)
    - Cozza, Carmen - Untitled (Box 5, Folder 861)
    - Dandelet, Thomas (Box 5, Folder 862)
    - Davey, Lycurgus "Bill" (Box 5, Folder 863)
    - Eliot, M - A History of the Catholics of Ulster (Box 5, Folder 864)
    - Ely, Christopher - Dissertation - Nineteenth-Century Russia (Box 5, Folder 865)
    - Encyclopedia of Aesthetics (Robert M. Adams opinion) (Box 5, Folder 866)
    - Encyclopedia of American Business (Citibank) Bruchey, Stuart (ed.) (Box 5, Folder 867)
    - Encyclopedia of American Colleges and Universities (Box 5, Folder 868)
    - Encyclopedia of National Parks (Box 5, Folder 869)
    - Encyclopedia of New Haven (Box 5, Folder 870)
    - Erikson, Kai - Approaches to Sociology (Box 5, Folder 871)
    - Erikson, Kai - (Misc.) (Box 5, Folder 872)
    - Finn, David - Lika Mutal (Box 5, Folder 873)
    - Fisher, Irving - The Works of Irving Fisher (Box 5, Folder 874)
    - Forte/Lalli - Listening to Classical American Popular Songs (Box 5, Folder 875)
    - Franco Papers (Box 5, Folder 876)
    - Gender/Gay-Lesbian Studies (Box 5, Folder 877)
    - Garten, Jeffrey (Dean) - SOM - (possible books) (Box 5, Folder 878)
    - Tape D90: "Mozambique: Riding Out the Storm" Alter-Ciné 1989 (Box 5, Folder 879)
    - Gill, Brendan - (Possible series of books to mark Yale's Tercentenary in 2001) (Box 5, Folder 880)
    - Gin, Kathy - Hot Shots (Box 5, Folder 881)
    - Graubard and Finn - Kerdalo (Box 5, Folder 882)
    - Hammer, Jane Ross - Richard Cromwell Biography (Box 5, Folder 883)
    - History of Jewish People, The (Jewish Museum) (Box 5, Folder 884)
    - Hidgson, Gofrey - Biography of Colonel House (Box 5, Folder 885)
    - Holocaust Encyclopedia, The (Lacquer, Walter) (Box 5, Folder 886)
    - Holquist/Shulman - Against Reductionism (Box 21, Folder 887)
    - Hyman - The Culture of the American Presidency (Box 21, Folder 888)
    - Jackson, Kenneth (misc.) (Box 5, Folder 889)
    - Katims, Milton (Box 5, Folder 890)
    - Kazdin - Current Perspectives in Psychology (Box 21, Folder 891)
    - Kennedy, Roger - The Burr ms (Box 5, Folder 892)
    - Kronman, Anthony T. - Prosecutorial Abuse (Box 5, Folder 894)
    - Laderman, Ezra - Untitled (Box 5, Folder 895)
    - Lamar, Howard R. - The Reader's Encyclopedia of the American West (Box 21, Folder 896)
    - Lapham, Lewis - Quarrels with Providence (Box 5, Folder 897)
    - Lazarus, Edward - Black Hills White Justice (Box 5, Folder 898)
    - Leung, Cecile (Sister) - The Language of the "Other" (Box 5, Folder 899)
    - Levin, Richard - The Work of the University (Box 21, Folder 900)
    - Levin, Richard - The Work of the University (Box 5, Folder 901)
    - Lindsay, John - Still On My Mind (Box 5, Folder 902)
    - Neighborhoods of New York City (Box 5, Folder 903)
    - McClatchy - Bright Pages (Box 21, Folder 904)
    - McClatchy - 300 Years of Yale Writers (Box 24, Folder 905)
    - Mellon, Andrew (biog.) (Box 5, Folder 906)
    - Moncreiff, Bob - Book on Bart Giamatti (Box 21, Folder 907)
    - Morgan - Who is Benjamin Franklin? (Box 5, Folder 908)
    - Moseley - John Yates Beall (Box 21, Folder 909)
    - Murphy, et al - Battleground Berlin (Box 5, Folder 910)
    - New Guide to American History (Box 5, Folder 911)
    - The New Republic: Heilbrunn Piece (Box 21, Folder 912)
    - Nordic Literature, Handbook of - Paperback Series (Box 5, Folder 914)
    - Oak Spring Garden Library: SYLVIA and Pomona (Box 5, Folder 915)
    - Paperback Series - Books (Proposed)
    - Pastor, Nicholas (Box 5, Folder 916)
    - E4, Jary - Creeds and Confessions of Faith (Box 5, Folder 917)
    - Pelikan, Jary - Jesus Through the Centuries (Illustrated) (Box 5, Folder 918)
    - Photocopying (Article on) (Box 5, Folder 919)
    - Posen Library of Jewish Culture (Box 21, Folder 920)
    - Reference Books (Box 5, Folder 921)
    - Rethinking Western Tradition - GENERAL (Box 21, Folder 922)
    - Robinson-Finn - BAC Book (Box 5, Folder 923)
    - Scully, Vincent - Vincent Scully: A Tribute (Box 5, Folder 924)
    - Sewall, Richard B. - A Kind of Passion: 100 Years of Teaching at Yale (Box 5, Folder 925)
    - Shapiro, Sidney - Autobiography and A Sampler of Chinese Lit. (Box 21, Folder 926)
    - Shearer/Derek/Ruth - Finland (Box 21, Folder 927)
    - Skelton/Martson/Painter - The Vinland Map (Revised) (Box 5, Folder 928)
    - Spaletti/Finn - Dupre, Giovanni (Box 5, Folder 929)
    - Warren, Robert Penn (Collected Poems) - John Burt (ed.) Brandeis University (Box 5, Folder 930)
    - Taylor, Charles H., Jr. - Images of the Journey in Dante's Comedy (Robert A. Lawrence) (Box 21, Folder 931)
    - Trias-Monge, Jose - Puerto Rico - The Need for a Second Look (Box 5, Folder 933)
    - Vietor, Anna Glen (Box 21, Folder 934)
    - Wallace, Tom - Men of the Book (Box 5, Folder 935)
    - Ward, Champion (Box 21, Folder 936)
    - Whelan - Ivy Leaguers Invent Football (Box 5, Folder 937)
    - Misc. - Books Proposed (Box 5, Folder 938)
  - YUP AAP/Beacon Press/Human Rights Watch
  - AAP
    - Annual Meeting
      - 1992 Mar 29 -Apr 1 (Box 14, Folder 939)
      - 1991 Mar 24-27 (Box 14, Folder 940)
    - Awards Program (Box 14, Folder 941)
    - Benjamin (Curtis) Award (Box 14, Folder 942)
    - Benjamin (Curtis) Award - Jason Epstein, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 943)
    - Board of Directors (Box 14, Folder 944)
    - Board of Directors Meetings
      - 1991 Sep 12-13 (Box 14, Folder 945)
      - 1990 Jun 28 (Box 14, Folder 946)
      - 1993 Sep 23 (Box 14, Folder 947)
      - 1994 Feb 8 (Box 14, Folder 948)
      - 1994 Mar (Box 14, Folder 949)
      - 1998 Feb (Box 14, Folder 950)
    - Committees (Box 14, Folder 951)
    - Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 952)
    - Freedom to Read Committee (Box 14, Folder 953)
    - Freedom to Read Committee/South Africa (Box 14, Folder 954)
    - Informational Media Guaranty Program (IMG) (Box 14, Folder 955)
    - International Freedom to Publish, 1992 December 7 (Box 14, Folder 956)
    - International Trade Group, The - UK/Europe Regional Committee (Box 14, Folder 957)
    - PSP Executive Council (Box 14, Folder 959)
    - Correspondence
      - -1993 (Box 22, Folder 960)
      - -1994 (Box 22, Folder 961)
    - Minutes, 1991 September 12-13 (Box 22, Folder 962)
    - Beacon Press
      - Board Meetings (Box 14, Folder 963)
      - Advisory Board (Box 14, Folder 964)
      - Correspondence, 1983- (Box 15, Folder 965 - 968)
      - Search Committee (Box 15, Folder 969)
    - Human Rights Watch
      - Applicants (Box 15, Folder 970)
      - Chinese Gulag, Committee to End the Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 971)
      - Human Rights Watch, 1989-1995 (Box 15)
      - Free Expression Project (Box 15, Folder 972)
      - Helsinki Watch (Box 15, Folder 973)
      - Pamphlet, News from…, etc. (Box 15, Folder 974)
      - World Report Advisory Board (Box 15, Folder 975)
- Publications Committee meeting agendas and minutes and awards won by Yale Press, 1962-2004; Accession 2006-A-146
  - Agendas and Minutes
    - 1968-1991 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 23)
    - 1992-2001 (Box 2, Folder 24 - 33)
  - Meetings
    - perm file
      - 1998 Jan 20 (Box 2, Folder 34)
      - 1998 Feb 17 (Box 2, Folder 35)
      - 1998 Mar 16 (Box 2, Folder 36)
      - 1998 Apr 20 (Box 2, Folder 37)
      - 1998 May 18 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1962-1966 (Box 2, Folder 39 - 43)
    - Perm file
      - 1998 Jun 15 (Box 3, Folder 44)
      - 1998 Aug 10 (Box 3, Folder 45)
      - 1998 Sep 14 (Box 3, Folder 46)
      - 1998 Oct 19 (Box 3, Folder 47)
      - 1998 Nov 16 (Box 3, Folder 48)
      - 1998 Dec 14 (Box 3, Folder 49)
      - 1999 Jan 19 (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - 1999 Feb 16 (Box 4, Folder 51)
      - 1999 Mar 15 (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - 1999 Apr 19 (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - 1999 May 17 (Box 4, Folder 54)
      - 1999 Jun 14 (Box 4, Folder 55)
      - Summer Procedures Mailing, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 56)
      - 1999 Sep 27 (Box 5, Folder 57 - 58)
      - 1999 Oct 18 (Box 5, Folder 59)
      - 1999 Nov 15 (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - 1999 Dec 13 (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - 2000 Jan 19 (Box 6, Folder 62)
      - 2000 Feb 22 (Box 6, Folder 63)
      - 2000 Mar 20 (Box 6, Folder 64)
      - 2000 Apr 17 (Box 6, Folder 65)
      - 2000 May 23 (Box 6, Folder 66)
      - 2000 Jun 19 (Box 7, Folder 67)
      - Summer Procedures Mailing, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 68)
      - 2000 Sep 25 (Box 7, Folder 69)
      - 2000 Oct 23 (Box 7, Folder 70)
      - 2000 Nov 20 (Box 7, Folder 71)
      - 2000 Dec 18 (Box 7, Folder 72)
      - 2001 Jan 22 (Box 8, Folder 73)
      - 2001 Feb 26 (Box 8, Folder 74)
      - 2001 Mar 19 (Box 8, Folder 75)
      - 2001 Apr 23 (Box 8, Folder 76)
      - 2001 May 23 (Box 8, Folder 77)
      - 2001 Jun 18 (Box 8, Folder 78)
      - Summer Procedures Mailing, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 79)
      - 2001 Sep 17 (Box 9, Folder 80)
      - 2001 Oct 15 (Box 9, Folder 81)
      - 2001 Nov 12 (Box 9, Folder 82)
      - 2001 Dec 10 (Box 9, Folder 83)
      - 2002 Jan 22 (Box 9, Folder 84)
      - 2002 Feb 19 (Box 9, Folder 85)
      - 2002 Mar 18 (Box 10, Folder 86)
      - 2002 Apr 15 (Box 10, Folder 87)
      - 2002 May 20 (Box 10, Folder 88)
      - 2002 Jun 1 (Box 10, Folder 89)
      - Summer Procedures Mailing, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 90)
      - 2002 Sep 23 (Box 10, Folder 91)
      - 2002 Oct 21 (Box 10, Folder 92)
      - 2002 Nov 18 (Box 10, Folder 93)
      - 2002 Dec 16 (Box 11, Folder 94)
      - 2003 Jan 21 (Box 11, Folder 95)
      - 2003 Feb 24 (Box 11, Folder 96)
      - 2003 Apr 1 (Box 11, Folder 97)
      - 2003 May 27 (Box 11, Folder 98)
      - 2003 Jun 1 (Box 11, Folder 99)
      - Summer Procedures Mailing, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 100)
      - 2003 Sep 1 (Box 11, Folder 101)
      - 2003 Oct 1 (Box 11, Folder 102)
      - 2003 Nov 17 (Box 11, Folder 103)
      - 2003 Dec 15 (Box 12, Folder 104)
      - 2004 Jan 21 (Box 12, Folder 105)
      - 2004 Feb 17 (Box 12, Folder 106)
      - 2004 Mar 22 (Box 12, Folder 107)
      - 2004 Apr 19 (Box 12, Folder 108)
      - 2004 May 17 (Box 12, Folder 109)
      - 2004 Jun 21 (Box 12, Folder 110)
      - Summer Procedures Mailing, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 111)
      - 2004 Sep 20 (Box 12, Folder 112)
      - 2004 Nov 1 (Box 12, Folder 113)
      - 2004 Dec 13 (Box 12, Folder 114)
    - Agendas, 1986-1996 (Box 13, Folder 115 - 125)
  - James Breasted Prize:In Search of History, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 126)
  - Professional/Scholarly Publishing Excellence -Arts:A Descriptive Catalogue of the Music of Charles Ives, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 127)
  - Bancroft Prize: Alan Gallay, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 128)
  - Carey-Thomas Award: Yale Series of Younger Poets, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 129)
  - Professional/Scholarly Publishing Excellence -Legal:Battered Women and Feminist Law Making, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 130)
  - Professional/Scholarly Publishing Excellence -Arts:Piano Roles, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 131)
  - Professional/Scholarly Publishing Excellence -Law:America and Law in the 20thCentury, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 132)
  - Professional/Scholarly Publishing -Honorable Mention -Arts:Monastic Vision, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 133)
  - Carey-Thomas Award -Honorable Mention:Papers of Benjamin Franklin, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 134)